In the darkest of times, love survives.
Desperate Journey is a history, war, thriller film directed by Annabel Jankel.
The true story of Freddie Knoller, a young Jewish man who flees Vienna following the Nazi
occupation in 1938 and finds solace in the vibrant world of Paris's burlesque scene.
Freddie Knoller, played by Lucas Lynggaard Tønnesen.
Jaqueline, played by Clara Rugaard.
Christos, played by Fernando Guallar.
Officer Kurt, played by Til Schweiger.
Mrs. Knoller, played by Sienna Guillory.
Raphael, played by Steven Berkoff.
2025 in film is an overview of events, including award ceremonies, festivals, a list of
country- and genre-specific lists of films released, and notable deaths.
Shochiku and Gaumont celebrated their 130th anniversaries; 20th Century Studios and Republic Pictures
celebrated their 90th anniversaries; and Studio Ghibli celebrated its 40th anniversary.
Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer's first musical film The Broadway Melody (1929), known for being the first sound
film to win the Academy Award for Best Picture, entered the public domain this year.
The film explores themes of nazi, biography,
historical figure, historical drama.
The tone is intense.